[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Inspired by a near death experience, Tom Smykowski, one of Peters co-workers in the movie Office Space, invented a game called Pay It Forward.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these methods do carnivorous plants use for capturing their prey?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Rapid leaf movements", "A sticky mucilage", "Vacuum sucking into a bladder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does the Giant Cowbird, a passerine bird found in South America, lay its eggs?", "correct_answer": "In other birds nests", "incorrect_answers": ["On rocks", "On balconies", "On the ground"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the popular song, in what city is the House of the Rising Sun located?", "correct_answer": "New Orleans", "incorrect_answers": ["Lexington", "San Francisco", "Dallas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would suffer from malnutrition?", "correct_answer": "50", "incorrect_answers": ["30", "20", "40"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average speed dolphins can reach?", "correct_answer": "16.5 km/hr", "incorrect_answers": ["25.5 km/hr", "14.5 km/hr", "38.5 km/hr"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning movie, directed by the Coen Brothers, features a pregnant small-town police chief?", "correct_answer": "Fargo", "incorrect_answers": ["No Country for Old Men", "The Big Lebowski", "The Man Who Wasnt There"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the bread variety called Tunnbrod originate?", "correct_answer": "Sweden", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "Switzerland", "Norway"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is generally accepted that this term, whose usage was reported by Newsweek in 1951, first appeared in Dr. Seusss book If I Ran the Zoo, where it names one of the comical, imaginary animals.", "correct_answer": "Nerd", "incorrect_answers": ["Yahoo", "Bluetooth", "Spam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie is this conversation from:\nNate Ruffin: Coach, that... was my team. They left it in my hands. \nJack Lengyel: No... no, they did not. They just left.", "correct_answer": "We Are Marshall", "incorrect_answers": ["The Westing Game", "Rocky 3", "Rudy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements is true about scorpions?", "correct_answer": "They give birth to their young one by one.", "incorrect_answers": ["They lay the eggs and they hatch almost immediately.", "They lay eggs which hatch after 2 weeks.", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Georgian town was the movie Facing the Giants filmed?", "correct_answer": "Albany", "incorrect_answers": ["Savannah", "Charlotte", "Blairesville"]}]